Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Anson Phelps Stokes correspondence and subject files, 1899-1929; Series II
  - Motion Pictures: "At Yale", 1921 (Box 91, Folder 1186)
  - Motion Pictures, 1924-1925 (Box 91, Folder 1187-1192)
  - Mott, John R., 1903-1920 (Box 91, Folder 1193)
  - Moyes-Freedman, 1922 (Box 92, Folder 1194)
  - Mu, 1901-1929 (Box 92, Folder 1195-1199)
  - Munger, Theodore M., 1901-1910 (Box 92, Folder 1200)
  - Munro, James A., 1907-1916 (Box 92, Folder 1201)
  - Murfee, H.O., 1907-1915 (Box 92, Folder 1202)
  - Murphy, Fred T., 1914-1920 (Box 92, Folder 1203)
  - Murphy, John K., 1917 (Box 92, Folder 1204)
  - Murray, Gilbert, 1911-1912 (Box 92, Folder 1205)
  - My, 1906-1924 (Box 92, Folder 1206)
  - Myers, Walter, 1911-1913 (Box 92, Folder 1207)
  - Na, 1903-1919 (Box 92, Folder 1208-1209)
  - Na, 1920-1927 (Box 93, Folder 1210)
  - Nea-Nev, 1902-1910 (Box 93, Folder 1211)
  - Nea-Nev, 1913-1929 (Box 93, Folder 1212)
  - Needham, Charles K., 1912 (Box 93, Folder 1213)
  - Needs, Departmental, undated (Box 93, Folder 1214)
  - Nettleton, George H., 1905-1928 (Box 93, Folder 1215-1216)
  - New-Ney, 1901-1927 (Box 93, Folder 1217-1219)
  - Newberry, Truman H., 1901-1918 (Box 93, Folder 1220)
  - Newberry, Memorial Organ, 1928-1929 (Box 93, Folder 1221)
  - New Haven Hospital, Directors" Dinner, 1929 (Box 93, Folder 1222)
  - Ni, 1900-1913 (Box 93, Folder 1223)
  - Ni, 1914-1929 (Box 94, Folder 1224)
  - No-Ny, 1901-1929 (Box 94, Folder 1225-1227)
  - Nolen, A. Eugene, 1911-1913 (Box 94, Folder 1228)
  - Noyes, Ernest H., 1913 (Box 94, Folder 1229)
  - Nursing, School of, 1919-1929 (Box 94, Folder 1230)
  - Oa-Oh, 1902-1929 (Box 94, Folder 1231-1232)
  - Oertel, Hanns, 1905-1915 (Box 94, Folder 1233-1235)
  - Oj-Or, 1905-1919 (Box 95, Folder 1236-1237)
  - Oj-Or, 1905-1913 (Box 95, Folder 1238)
  - Olds, Irving S., 1911-1913 (Box 95, Folder 1239)
  - O"Neal, Emmet, 1912-1915 (Box 95, Folder 1240)
  - Os-Oz, 1903-1929 (Box 95, Folder 1241-1243)
  - Osborn, Henry M., 1902-1912 (Box 95, Folder 1244)
  - Osborn, Minott A., 1913-1922 (Box 95, Folder 1245-1247)
  - Osborn, Minott A., 1923-1927 (Box 96, Folder 1248-1249)
  - Osborn, Norris G., 1905-1919 (Box 96, Folder 1250)
  - Osborne, Thomas Mott, 1915-1916 (Box 96, Folder 1251)
  - Osler, William, 1912-1913 (Box 96, Folder 1252)
  - Ostrander, Harry J., 1909-1929 (Box 96, Folder 1253-1255)
  - Overton, Winfield S., 1917 (Box 96, Folder 1256)
  - Oviatt, Edwin, 1906-1926 (Box 96, Folder 1257-1261)
  - Pa-Pap, 1901-1928 (Box 97, Folder 1262-1265)
  - Palmer, Arthur H., 1901-1917 (Box 97, Folder 1266)
  - Palmer, Charles Ray, 1901-1913 (Box 97, Folder 1267)
  - Par, 1899-1928 (Box 97, Folder 1268-1271)
  - Pardee, William S., 1913-1915 (Box 97, Folder 1272)
  - Parker, Edwin P., 1901-1919 (Box 97, Folder 1273-1275)
  - Parker, Horatio, 1901-1919 (Box 97, Folder 1276-1277)
  - Parkhurst, Charles H., 1913 (Box 98, Folder 1278)
  - Parks, G. Elton, 1911-1915 (Box 98, Folder 1279)
  - Parmelee, Julius H., 1912 (Box 98, Folder 1280)
  - Parsons, Herbert, 1917 (Box 98, Folder 1281)
  - Parsons, William Usher, 1911-1912 (Box 98, Folder 1282)
  - Partridge, William O., 1911 (Box 98, Folder 1283)
  - Pas-Pay, 1900-1929 (Box 98, Folder 1284-1285)
  - Pasco, Martin K., 1912 (Box 98, Folder 1286)
  - Patchin, Ira H., 1915-1916 (Box 98, Folder 1287-1288)
  - Pathe Exchange, Inc., 1923 (Box 98, Folder 1289)
  - Pe, 1902-1914 (Box 98, Folder 1290-1292)
  - Pe, 1915-1929 (Box 99, Folder 1293-1296)
  - Peabody, Endicott, 1901-1921 (Box 99, Folder 1297)
  - Peabody Museum, 1908-1928 (Box 99, Folder 1298-1299)
  - Peck, R.S., & Company, 1912 (Box 99, Folder 1300)
  - Peck, Tracy, 1900-1919 (Box 99, Folder 1301)
  - Peet, R.A., 1912 (Box 99, Folder 1302)
  - Penny, Thomas, 1912-1913 (Box 99, Folder 1303)
  - Pepper, Mr. & Mrs. George Wharton, 1912-1918 (Box 99, Folder 1304-1305)
  - Perrin, Bernadotte, 1901-1918 (Box 99, Folder 1306)
  - Perrin, Lee J., 1906-1913 (Box 99, Folder 1307)
  - Personnel Bureau, 1926-1927 (Box 99, Folder 1308)
  - Petition, Treaty of Peace, League of Nations, 1919 (Box 99, Folder 1309)
  - Ph, 1900-1927 (Box 100, Folder 1310-1313)
  - Phelps, Edward J., 1903-1909 April (Box 100, Folder 1314-1320)
  - Phelps, Edward J., 1913 May-1926 (Box 101, Folder 1321-1325)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1901-1927 (Box 101, Folder 1326-1327)
  - Phillips, Andrew W., 1899-1911 (Box 101, Folder 1328-1329)
  - Pi, 1901-1916 (Box 101, Folder 1330-1331)
  - Pi, 1917-1928 (Box 102, Folder 1332)
  - Pierce, Roger, 1913-1918 (Box 102, Folder 1333)
  - Pilgrim Tercentenary, 1920 (Box 102, Folder 1334)
  - Pinchot, Gifford, 1900-1913 (Box 102, Folder 1335)
  - Pirsson, Louis V., 1900-1919 (Box 102, Folder 1336)
  - Pl, 1905-1924 (Box 102, Folder 1337-1338)
  - Platt, Livingston, 1916-1925 (Box 102, Folder 1339)
  - Plattsburg, Junior, Inc., 1917 (Box 102, Folder 1340)
  - Plimpton Press, 1914-1916 (Box 102, Folder 1341)
  - Po, 1901-1907 (Box 102, Folder 1342)
  - Po, 1911-1915 (Box 102, Folder 1343-1344)
  - Po, 1916-1929 (Box 103, Folder 1345-1346)
  - Polk, Frank L., 1906-1915 (Box 103, Folder 1347-1348)
  - Polk, Frank L., 1917-1921 (Box 103, Folder 1349)
  - Porter, Frank C., 1900-1920 (Box 103, Folder 1350)
  - Porter, John Addison: University Prize, 1919-1927 (Box 103, Folder 1351)
  - Portraits, 1912, 1928 (Box 103, Folder 1353)
  - Pr-Ps, 1900-1920 (Box 103, Folder 1354-1357)
  - Pr-Ps, 1921-1929 (Box 104, Folder 1358-1359)
  - Preachers, 1903-1927 (Box 104, Folder 1360-1366)
  - President"s reception, 1923 (Box 104, Folder 1367)
  - President"s reports, 1924 (Box 104, Folder 1368)
  - Princeton, 1928 (Box 104, Folder 1369)
  - Printing Department, 1929 (Box 104, Folder 1370)
  - Pritchett, Henry S., 1905-1920 (Box 105, Folder 1371)
  - Prizes, 1923 (Box 105, Folder 1372)
  - Prizes, 1925-1927 (Box 105, Folder 1373-1375)
  - Prizes, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 1376)
  - Prospective students, 1928 (Box 105, Folder 1377)
  - Protestant Encyclopaedia, 1913 (Box 105, Folder 1378)
  - Pu-Py, 1902-1929 (Box 105, Folder 1379)
  - Publicity, 1923-1929 (Box 105, Folder 1380-1384)
  - Q, 1907-1923 (Box 106, Folder 1385)
  - Ra, 1900-1929 (Box 106, Folder 1386-1387)
  - Radio, correspondence regarding talk on Yale, 1923-1924 (Box 106, Folder 1388)
  - Railroad rates, 1905-1928 (Box 106, Folder 1389)
  - Re, 1905-1929 (Box 106, Folder 1390-1393)
  - Recitation Schedule, 1927 (Box 106, Folder 1394)
  - Reconstruction lectures, 1918 (Box 106, Folder 1395)
  - Reed, Edward B., 1902-1921 (Box 106, Folder 1396)
  - Registration, 1902-1928 (Box 107, Folder 1397)
  - Reorganization, 1919 (Box 107, Folder 1398-1403)
  - Rettger, Leo F., 1918-1924 (Box 107, Folder 1404)
  - Rew, Irwin, 1912-1924 (Box 107)
  - Rh, 1905-1928 (Box 107, Folder 1406)
  - Ri, 1901-1929 (Box 108, Folder 1407-1410)
  - Rice, Frank J., 1911-1916 (Box 108, Folder 1411)
  - Richards, Howard Jr., 1912-1913 (Box 108, Folder 1412)
  - Riddell, William Renwick, 1916-1921 (Box 108, Folder 1413)
  - Riot, 1919 (Box 108, Folder 1414)
  - Ripley, Alfred L., 1901-1929 (Box 108, Folder 1415-1417)
  - Ripley, Julian A., 1912-1913 (Box 109, Folder 1418)
  - Ro, 1899-1929 (Box 109, Folder 1419-1427)
  - Robbins, Howard C., 1916 (Box 109, Folder 1428)
  - Robbins, Richard W., 1912-1913 (Box 109, Folder 1429)
  - Robertson, Edwin W., 1913-1915 (Box 109, Folder 1430)
  - Robey, Louis W., 1913 (Box 109, Folder 1431)
  - Rockefeller clippings, 1905 (Box 110, Folder 1432)
  - Rogers, Francis, 1915-1916 (Box 110, Folder 1433)
  - Rogers, Henry T., 1904-1922 (Box 110, Folder 1434-1435)
  - Rogers, Henry Wade, 1901-1918 (Box 110, Folder 1436-1439)
  - Rogers, James Gamble, 1917-1928 (Box 110, Folder 1440)
  - Rogers, James Grafton, 1901-1928 (Box 110, Folder 1441)
  - Rogers, Randolph P., 1912 (Box 110, Folder 1442)
  - Rollins, Carl P., 1918-1928 (Box 110, Folder 1443)
  - Ross, G. A. Johnston, 1912-1913 (Box 110, Folder 1444)
  - Ru-Rz, 1903-1914 (Box 110, Folder 1445-1446)
  - Ru-Rz, 1915-1929 (Box 111, Folder 1447-1448)
  - Rudd, A.H., 1914-1915 (Box 111, Folder 1449)
  - Runk, Louis B., 1907-1915 (Box 111, Folder 1450)
  - Russell, Talcott H., 1909-1913 (Box 111, Folder 1451)
  - Russell, Thomas H. Jr., 1912 (Box 111, Folder 1452)
  - S-Sam, 1901-1929 (Box 111, Folder 1453-1456)
  - Sabin, Joseph F., 1913-1919 (Box 111, Folder 1457)
  - Sage Hall dedication, 1922, n. d. (Box 111, Folder 1458)
  - St. Louis Exposition, 1903-1904 (Box 111, Folder 1459)
  - Salaries, 1905-1919 (Box 111, Folder 1460)
  - Sallman, William H., 1900-1918 (Box 112, Folder 1461-1465)
  - San-Saz, 1900-1927 (Box 112, Folder 1463-1466)
  - Sanders, Frank K., 1901-1912 (Box 112, Folder 1467)
  - Sanderson, George A., 1913-1914 (Box 112, Folder 1468)
  - Sanderson, Robert Lewis, 1902-1929 (Box 112, Folder 1469)
  - Sargent, E. R., 1915-1918 (Box 112, Folder 1470)
  - Sargent, Henry B., 1902-1920 (Box 112, Folder 1471)
  - Sawyer, George P., 1912-1914 (Box 112, Folder 1472)
  - Sea-Sec, 1913-1923 (Box 112, Folder 1473)
  - Sch, 1902-1929 (Box 113, Folder 1474-1476)
  - Scholarship awards: form letter to Alumni Association, 1922-1923 (Box 113, Folder 1477)
  - Scholarships, 1923-1925 (Box 113, Folder 1478)
  - Schuchert, Charles, 1904-1920 (Box 113, Folder 1479-1480)
  - Schwab, John C., 1901-1915 (Box 113, Folder 1481-1484)
  - Sci-Scz, 1901-1929 (Box 114, Folder 1485-1486)
  - Scott, Charles F., 1912-1928 (Box 114, Folder 1487)
  - Scoville, Samuel Jr., 1911-1913 (Box 114, Folder 1488)
  - Se, 1901-1929 (Box 114, Folder 1489-1492)
  - Secretary"s Office, 1919 (Box 114, Folder 1493)
  - Secretaryship, letters re, 1927 (Box 114, Folder 1494)
  - Seymour, George Dudley, 1901-1929 (Box 114, Folder 1495-1496)
  - Sh, 1901-1912 (Box 114, Folder 1497-1498)
  - Sh, 1913-1929 (Box 115, Folder 1499-1503)
  - Shaffer, Carroll, 1911-1915 (Box 115, Folder 1504)
  - Shaw, Wilfred B., 1913-1917 (Box 115, Folder 1505)
  - Sheffield, James B., 1901-1913 (Box 115, Folder 1507)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, 1918-1920 (Box 115, Folder 1508)
  - Sheldon, Winthrop D., 1912 (Box 115, Folder 1509)
  - Sheldon, Harrison T., 1913 (Box 115, Folder 1510)
  - Shepard, Frederick J., 1912-1913 (Box 115, Folder 1511)
  - Sherrill, Charles H., 1901-1914 (Box 115, Folder 1512)
  - Sherrill, Charles H., 1905-1928 (Box 115, Folder 1513)
  - Si-Sk, 1902-1929 (Box 116, Folder 1514-1516)
  - Skiddy, W.W., 1902-1912 (Box 116, Folder 1517)
  - Sl, 1901-1929 (Box 116, Folder 1518-1519)
  - Slone, Henry J., 1909-1927 (Box 116, Folder 1520)
  - Slone, William, 1900-1918 (Box 116, Folder 1521)
  - Slone, William D., 1909-1911 (Box 116, Folder 1522)
  - Sm, 1903-1927 (Box 116, Folder 1523)
  - Smith, 1901-1929 (Box 117, Folder 1524-1527)
  - Smith, David S., 1903-1929 (Box 117, Folder 1528)
  - Smith, Emily A., 1912-1913 (Box 117, Folder 1529)
  - Smith, Herbert E., 1901-1919 (Box 117, Folder 1530)
  - Smith, Percy F., 1913-1920 (Box 117, Folder 1531)
  - Sn-So, 1903-1917 (Box 117, Folder 1532-1533)
  - Sneath, E. Hersey, 1903-1919 (Box 117, Folder 1534)
  - Social and Religious Research, Institute of, 1924 (Box 117, Folder 1535)
  - Social case work lectures, 1923-1924 (Box 118, Folder 1536)
  - Sousa, John Phillips, 1912, undated (Box 118, Folder 1537)
  - Sp, 1901-1929 (Box 118, Folder 1538-1539)
  - Speaking engagements, 1923-1924 (Box 118, Folder 1540)
  - Sperr, Robert E., 1901-1920 (Box 118, Folder 1541)
  - Spitzer, Carl B., 1910-1914 (Box 118, Folder 1542)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall, 1917 (Box 118, Folder 1543)
  - Speck, William A., 1913-1918 (Box 118, Folder 1544)
  - Sta, 1904-1924 (Box 118, Folder 1545-1546)
  - Statistics, 1920-1924 (Box 118, Folder 1547)
  - Ste, 1900-1929 (Box 118, Folder 1548-1550)
  - Ste, 1900-1929 (Box 119, Folder 1551)
  - Stearns, Alfred E., 1905-1921 (Box 119, Folder 1552)
  - Steiner, Bernard C., 1912-1915 (Box 119, Folder 1553)
  - Steiner, Walter R., 1914-1915 (Box 119, Folder 1554)
  - Steinert Collection Exhibition, 1929 (Box 119, Folder 1555)
  - Sterling, John W., 1909-1921 (Box 119, Folder 1556)
  - Sterling bequest, suggestions regarding the use of, 1919-1925 (Box 119, Folder 1557)
  - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory, 1923 (Box 119, Folder 1558)
  - Sterling Fellowships in Graduate School, 1925 (Box 119, Folder 1559)
  - Sterling Fund, 1907-1919 (Box 119, Folder 1560-1561)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine dedication, 1924-1925 (Box 119, Folder 1562)
  - Sterling Memorial Library, 1925-1929 (Box 119, Folder 1563-1565)
  - Sti, 1901-1928 (Box 120, Folder 1566)
  - Sto, 1900-1929 (Box 120, Folder 1567-1570)
  - Stoddard, Henry, 1912-1913 (Box 120, Folder 1571)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1905-1912 (Box 120, Folder 1572-1575)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1913-1917 (Box 121, Folder 1576-1584)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1918-1921 (Box 122, Folder 1585-1591)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1923-1929 (Box 122, Folder 1592)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps: memo regarding his Yale memorabilia collection, 1927 (Box 122, Folder 1593)
  - Stokes, Frederick A., 1911-1912 (Box 123, Folder 1594)
  - Stokes, Harold Phelps, 1911-1915 (Box 123, Folder 1595)
  - Stokes, W.E.D., 1904-1919 (Box 123, Folder 1596-1597)
  - Str-Stz, 1901-1926 (Box 123, Folder 1598-1599)
  - Strathcona, Lord, 1914-1915 (Box 123, Folder 1600)
  - Student"s Army Training Corps, general orders of, 1918 (Box 123, Folder 1601)
  - Student"s Army Training Corps, 1918 (Box 123, Folder 1602-1603)
  - Su-Sz, 1902-1929 (Box 123, Folder 1604-1606)
  - Sutherland portrait, 1923-1924 (Box 124, Folder 1607)
  - Swan, Thomas W., 1916-1926 (Box 124, Folder 1608-1611)
  - Swayne, Noah H., 1912-1913 (Box 124, Folder 1612)
  - Sweden, Prince William of, 1927 (Box 124, Folder 1613)
  - Ta-Tat, 1901-1929 (Box 124, Folder 1614-1615)
  - Taft, Horace D., 1902-1924 (Box 124, Folder 1616)
  - Taft, William H., 1901-1928 (Box 124, Folder 1617-1619)
  - Taft portrait, 1925 (Box 124, Folder 1620)
  - Taxation, 1899-1913 (Box 124, Folder 1621)
  - Tay, 1901-1914 (Box 124, Folder 1622)
  - Tay, 1915-1928 (Box 125, Folder 1623)
  - Taylor, Andrew S., 1904-1920 (Box 125, Folder 1624-1625)
  - Taylor, Edward C., 1908-1919 (Box 125, Folder 1626)
  - Te, 1902-1911 (Box 125, Folder 1627)
  - Te, 1913-1929 (Box 125, Folder 1628-1929)
  - Telephone directories, 1913 (Box 125, Folder 1630)
  - Terry, Dwight H., 1903-1919 (Box 125, Folder 1631)
  - Terry Lectureship, 1923-1927 (Box 125, Folder 1632-1634)
  - Th, 1900-1912 (Box 125, Folder 1635-1636)
  - Th, 1913-1929 (Box 126, Folder 1637-1640)
  - Thacher, Sherman D., 1909-1923 (Box 126, Folder 1641)
  - Thacher, Thomas and Thomas D., 1901-1920 (Box 126, Folder 1642)
  - Thacher, William L., 1906-1912 (Box 126, Folder 1643)
  - Thayer, William G., 1905-1920 (Box 126, Folder 1644)
  - Thomas, Arthur A., 1911-1924 (Box 126, Folder 1645-1646)
  - Thompson, Everand, 1907-1915 (Box 126, Folder 1647)
  - Thompson, George E., 1911-1920 (Box 126, Folder 1648)
  - Thurston, R. C. Ballard, 1912-1929 (Box 126, Folder 1649)
  - Ti, 1901-1929 (Box 126, Folder 1650-1651)
  - Tibbals, Charles A., 1912 (Box 127, Folder 1652)
  - Tiffany & Company, 1912-1920 (Box 127, Folder 1653)
  - Tileston, Wilder, 1909-1921 (Box 127, Folder 1654)
  - Tilson, John Q., 1901-1920 (Box 127, Folder 1655)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1905-1921 (Box 127, Folder 1656)
  - To, 1900-1929 (Box 127, Folder 1657-1659)
  - Tombo, Rudolf Jr., 1906-1914 (Box 127, Folder 1660)
  - Torrey, Charles C., 1900-1926 (Box 127, Folder 1661)
  - Toumey, James W., 1900-1922 (Box 127, Folder 1662-1664)
  - Tr-Ty, 1900-1929 (Box 128, Folder 1665-1671)
  - Tracy, John C., 1915-1926 (Box 128, Folder 1672)
  - Traffic Conference, 1921 (Box 128, Folder 1673)
  - Treadway, Charles T., 1914 (Box 128, Folder 1674)
  - Treasurer"s Office, 1909-1929 (Box 128, Folder 1675)
  - Trumbull, John Memorial Services, 1928 (Box 128, Folder 1676)
  - Tuition, Graduate School, undated (Box 128, Folder 1677)
  - Tully, Thomas A., 1911-1913 (Box 128, Folder 1678)
  - Tuttle, Roger W., 1914-1922 (Box 129, Folder 1679)
  - Tuttle, Morehouse and Taylor Co., 1911-1917 (Box 129, Folder 1680)
  - Twichell, Burton P., 1920-1921 (Box 129, Folder 1681)
  - Twichell, Joseph H., 1912-1913 (Box 129, Folder 1682)
  - Tyson, Levering, 1914-1918 (Box 129, Folder 1683)
  - U, 1903-1929 (Box 129, Folder 1684-1687)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1928 (Box 129, Folder 1688)
  - Underwood, Clara B., 1911-1914 (Box 129, Folder 1689)
  - Underwood, Eugene B., 1911-1925 (Box 129, Folder 1690)
  - United Graduates Reunion Dinner, 1492 Dinner, 1914 (Box 129, Folder 1691)
  - Universal Pictures Corporation, 1923 (Box 129, Folder 1692)
  - University Council, 1922-1923 (Box 129, Folder 1693)
  - University Emergency Council, 1917 (Box 129, Folder 1694)
  - University Glee Club, 1926 (Box 129, Folder 1695)
  - University Theatre, 1926-1927 (Box 129, Folder 1696)
  - Va, 1900-1916 (Box 129, Folder 1697-1698)
  - Va, 1917-1929 (Box 130, Folder 1699)
  - Van Dyck and Company, Inc., 1913 (Box 130, Folder 1700)
  - Ve-Vy, 1901-1919 (Box 130, Folder 1701-1702)
  - Ve-Vy, 1926-1927 (Box 130, Folder 1703)
  - Ve-Vy, 1920-1929 (Box 130, Folder 1704)
  - Vincent, George E., 1905-1929 (Box 130, Folder 1705)
  - Waa-Wal, 1900-1909 (Box 130, Folder 1706)
  - Waa-Wal, 1911-1929 (Box 130, Folder 1707-1708)
  - Walden, Percy T., 1925 (Box 130, Folder 1709)
  - Walker, William John, 1912 (Box 130, Folder 1710)
  - Walker, Williston, 1901-1919 (Box 130, Folder 1711-1712)
  - Walker, Williston, 1920-1921 May (Box 131, Folder 1713-1714)
  - Walker, Williston, 1921-1922 (Box 131, Folder 1715)
  - Walton, J. Barnard, 1911-1912 (Box 131, Folder 1716)
  - Wam-Waz, 1901-1929 (Box 131, Folder 1717-1721)
  - War, Mexican, Honor Roll, 1929 (Box 131, Folder 1722)
  - War, Revolutionary, Honor Roll, 1929 (Box 131, Folder 1723)
  - Wars, Spanish-Phillipine-Boxer, Honor Roll, 1929 (Box 131, Folder 1724)
  - War of 1812, Honor Roll, 1929 (Box 131, Folder 1725)
  - War Portrait Exhibition, 1921 (Box 132, Folder 1726)
  - War Record, 1920 (Box 132, Folder 1727)
  - Ward, Wilfred, 1914-1915 (Box 132, Folder 1728)
  - Warren, Charles H., 1922-1928 (Box 132, Folder 1729)
  - Warren, Charles Howard, 1914 (Box 132, Folder 1730)
  - Warren, Frederick M., 1902-1922 (Box 132, Folder 1731)
  - Warwick, H.S., 1913 (Box 132, Folder 1732)
  - Waters, N. McGee, 1912-1913 (Box 132, Folder 1733)
  - Watrous, Eliot, 1912-1913 (Box 132, Folder 1734)
  - We, 1901-1928 (Box 132, Folder 1735-1740)
  - Weir, John F., 1901-1914 (Box 132, Folder 1741-1742)
  - Welch, Lewis S., 1900-1928 (Box 132, Folder 1743)
  - Welch, Lewis S., 1900-1928 (Box 133, Folder 1744-1745)
  - Wells, E.H., 1911-1912 (Box 133, Folder 1746)
  - West, Thomas H. Jr., 1913-1915 (Box 133, Folder 1747)
  - West Point, 1924-1926 (Box 133, Folder 1748)
  - Western New England Magazine, 1913 (Box 133, Folder 1749)
  - Western Union Telegram, [ca. 1911-1913] (Box 133, Folder 1750)
  - Western Union Telegram, [ca. 1915-1917] (Box 133, Folder 1751)
  - Western Union Telegram, [ca. 1917-1919] (Box 133, Folder 1752)
  - Western Union Telegram, [ca. 1914-1915] (Box 133, Folder 1753)
  - Western Union Telegram, [ca. 1919-1929] (Box 134, Folder 1754)
  - Wh, 1900-1909 (Box 134, Folder 1755-1757)
  - Wh, 1911-1929 (Box 134, Folder 1758-1761)
  - Wheeler, L.R., 1911-1913 (Box 134, Folder 1762)
  - White, Edwin, 1912 (Box 134, Folder 1763)
  - Whitney, Eli, 1913 (Box 134, Folder 1764)
  - Whiton, James M., 1911-1913 (Box 134, Folder 1765)
  - Whittlesey, George N., 1912-1913 (Box 135, Folder 1766)
  - Wi, 1900-1909 (Box 135, Folder 1767-1768)
  - Wi, 1911-1929 (Box 135, Folder 1769-1774)
  - Wilder, Amos P., 1914-1925 (Box 135, Folder 1775)
  - Williams, Arthur C., 1905-1911 (Box 136, Folder 1776)
  - Williams, Arthur C., [ca. 1905-1911] (Box 136, Folder 1777)
  - Williams, Charles D., 1911-1913 (Box 136, Folder 1778)
  - Williams, F. Wells, 1907-1914 (Box 136, Folder 1779)
  - Williams, Talcott, 1911-1912 (Box 136, Folder 1780)
  - Winchester, Mrs. [Williams Hart Winchester Hospital], 1919-1920 (Box 136, Folder 1781)
  - Winslow, C.E.A., 1915-1922 (Box 136, Folder 1782)
  - Winslow, C.E.A. Report on sanitary conditions in the University dining hall, undated (Box 136, Folder 1783)
  - Winterkotham, John H., 1921 (Box 136, Folder 1784)
  - Winternitz, Milton C., 1917-1929 (Box 136, Folder 1785-1786)
  - Wo, 1901-1929 (Box 136, Folder 1787-1790)
  - Woodman, Francis C., 1911-1912 (Box 137, Folder 1791)
  - Woodward, George, 1907-1924 (Box 137, Folder 1792)
  - Woodward, Robert S., 1909-1914 (Box 137, Folder 1793)
  - Woolley, Edgar M., 1923-1927 (Box 137, Folder 1794)
  - Woolsey, Theodore S., 1902-1922 (Box 137, Folder 1795)
  - Woolsey Hall, 1911-1924 (Box 137, Folder 1796)
  - Worcester, Edwin D. (Box 137, Folder 1797)
  - Worcester, Elwood, 1911-1913 (Box 137, Folder 1798)
  - Wr-Wz, 1903-1929 (Box 137, Folder 1799)
  - Wrexham, 1918-1923 (Box 137, Folder 1800)
  - Wright, Henry B., 1901-1919 (Box 137, Folder 1801)
  - Wright, Henry B. Memorial, 1926 (Box 137, Folder 1802)
  - Wright, Henry P., 1899-1914 (Box 137, Folder 1803-1804)
  - Wright, James, 1917-1918 (Box 137, Folder 1805)
  - Wyant, G.G., 1918-1925 (Box 137, Folder 1806)
  - Ya, 1901-1925 (Box 137, Folder 1807)
  - Yale, 1915-1928 (Box 137, Folder 1808)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1905-1927 (Box 138, Folder 1809)
  - Yale Banner and Pot Pourri, 1918 (Box 138, Folder 1810)
  - Yale Club, New York City, 1908-1929 (Box 138, Folder 1811)
  - Yale Co-operative Corporation, 1911-1913 (Box 138, Folder 1812)
  - Yale: Correspondence re: Photographs of buildings, paintings, etc., 1903-1929 (Box 138, Folder 1813)
  - Yale Daily News, 1915-1929 (Box 138, Folder 1814)
  - Yale Glee Club, 1926 (Box 138, Folder 1815)
  - Yale-In-China, 1913-1927 (Box 138, Folder 1816)
  - Yale-In-China, 1918-1928 (Box 138, Folder 1817)
  - Yale name, use of, 1911-1928 (Box 138, Folder 1818-1820)
  - Yale name and seal, use of, 1923-1926 (Box 138, Folder 1821)
  - Yale name and seal, use of, 1928-1929 (Box 138, Folder 1822)
  - Yale, use of name in motion pictures, 1928 (Box 138, Folder 1823)
  - Yale and New Haven, 1921 (Box 138, Folder 1824)
  - Yale Press, 1915-1918 (Box 139, Folder 1825-1826)
  - Yale Publishing, 1908-1920 (Box 139, Folder 1827)
  - Yale University: Encyclopaedia Brittanica, 1929 (Box 139, Folder 1828)
  - Yale University, gifts to, 1928-1929 (Box 139, Folder 1829)
  - Yale University, Visitors to, 1927-1929 (Box 139, Folder 1830)
  - Ye, 1908-1926 (Box 139, Folder 1831)
  - Yo-Yu, 1908-1929 (Box 139, Folder 1832)
  - Z, 1903-1929 (Box 139, Folder 1833)
- Correspondence and subject files, 1929-1953; Series III
  - A, 1929-1939 (Box 140, Folder 1-10)
  - A, 1939-1952 (Box 141, Folder 11-20)
  - Academic costume, 1934 (Box 142, Folder 21)
  - Academic freedom, undated (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - Academic rank, 1937-1938 (Box 142, Folder 23)
  - Accelerator building, 1952 (Box 142, Folder 24)
  - Admissions, Board of, 1934-1942 (Box 142, Folder 25)
  - Admissions, Board of, 1944-1950 (Box 142, Folder 26)
  - Admissions, Board of: replies from preparatory schools, 1937-1938 (Box 142, Folder 27)
  - Alcohol studies: Haggard, Howard W., 1943-1946 (Box 142, Folder 28)
  - Alcohol studies, 1946-1952 (Box 142, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Activities, Committee on Coordination of, 1941 (Box 142, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Associations, 1942-1950 (Box 142, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Board, 1936-1940 (Box 142, Folder 32-35)
  - Alumni Board, 1940-1953 (Box 143, Folder 36-42)
  - Alumni Fellows, 1939-1953 (Box 144, Folder 43-61)
  - Alumni Forum, 1941 (Box 145, Folder 62)
  - Alumni Fund, 1939-1952 (Box 145, Folder 63-68)
  - Alumni Magazine, 1950 (Box 145, Folder 69)
  - Alumni meetings, 1939-1941 (Box 145, Folder 69a)
  - Alumni meetings & dinners: speakers at, 1938 (Box 145, Folder 69b)